(Leonard:)With any luck, tonight will be the night
my sleep apnea kills me.
Did you ask for the chicken to be diced,
not shredded?
(Sheldon:)- Yes.
- Even though the menu specifies shredded?
- Brown rice, not white?
(Sheldon:)- Yes.
- Did you stop and get the hot mustard?
- Did you pick up the low-sodium soy sauce?
(Sheldon:)- Yes.
- Thank you.
(Raj:)You're welcome.
(Sheldon:)What took you so long?
- Just sit down and eat.
- Fine.
All right, it's shredded.
What do you want me to do?
(Sheldon:)I want you to check
before you accept the order.
(Raj:)Sorry.
(Sheldon:)Were you distracted
by the possibility...
(Sheldon:)...that Koothrappali might have intercourse
with Penny tonight?
(Leonard:)He's not going to have intercourse
with Penny.
(Sheldon:)Then there's no excuse for this chicken.
You know, this situation with Koothrappali
brings to mind a story from my childhood.
(Howard:)Oh, goody,
more tales from the panhandle.